in this tutorial we'll be going over an
在本教程中，我们将介绍一个
example of when the measurement tool
例如，当测量工具
would come in handy in inkscape and the
在Inkscape和
example we'll be working with in this
我们将在本文中使用的示例
lesson is the Gmail logo now this is a
课程是Gmail徽标现在这是一个
rasterized PNG image that I have copied
我复制的光栅化的PNG图像
and pasted into inkscape if I zoom in
如果我放大，会粘贴到Inkscape中
here you can see the pixelation let's
在这里您可以看到像素化，让我们
say we wanted to trace a vector copy of
假设我们想要追踪一份
this logo to work with the way that you
此徽标与您的工作方式
would normally do that is by creating
通常会通过创建
individual shapes in this example it
本例中的各个形状都是它
would be rectangles that make up the
将是组成
design here now the problem with the
在这里设计现在的问题是
Gmail logo is that these lines here go
Gmail的徽标是这样写的
at an unusual angle normally when you're
在一个不寻常的角度通常当你在
working with inkscape you can rotate
使用Inkscape可以旋转
objects in 15 degree increments or you
以15度为增量的对象或您
can rotate them freehand now the problem
现在可以徒手旋转他们的问题了吗
with rotating them freehand is that
徒手旋转它们，就是
you'll have to guess what size the
你得猜一猜这件衣服的尺寸
rectangle has to be before rotating it
矩形必须在旋转之前放置
otherwise it won't be accurate so this
否则就不会准确，所以这个
is where the measurement tool comes in
是测量工具的用武之地
handy
得心应手
so I'm going to click on the logo to
所以我要点击徽标来
select it and I'm going to bring down
选择它，我就会把它拿下来
the opacity in half just so I can see
把不透明度减半，这样我就能看到
the measurements that I'm taking on top
我在上面测量的尺寸
of it and then I'm going to zoom in here
然后我要放大这里
and I want to take a measurement of this
我想要测量一下这一点
line right here to find out what this
就在这里排队，看看这是什么
angle is and to do that I'm going to use
角度是，为了做到这一点，我将使用
the measurement tool which is located
所在的测量工具
over here in the toolbar or you can
在这里的工具栏中，或者您可以
access it by pressing the letter M on
按字母M On即可访问它
the keyboard
键盘
and with that tool enabled I'm going to
启用该工具后，我将
bring my cursor over to the edge of the
将我的光标移到
line here and I'm going to click and
行在这里，我将点击并
drag a line
拖出一条线
that goes along the edge of the logo
沿着徽标的边缘
there and as you can see the measurement
在那里，正如你所看到的测量
that I'm working with is 37.14 now this
我正在使用的是37.14，现在这个
isn't totally accurate so I'm just going
不是完全准确的，所以我只是去
to change this a little bit just to make
稍微改变一下这一点只是为了
sure it's flush against the edge there
当然，它与边沿平齐。
okay now we have a more accurate
好的，现在我们有了一个更准确的
measurement this angle right here is
在这里测量这个角度是
36.95 so I'm going to remember that
36.95所以我会记住
number and now I'm going to create
数字，现在我要创建
guides and change the angles of those
辅助线并更改这些对象的角度
guides to match that right there so let
导游要与之匹配，所以让我们
me go back to my selection tool
我返回到我的选择工具
now I'm going to enable the ruler on my
现在我要启用我的尺子
canvas so that I can create my guides if
画布，以便我可以在以下情况下创建辅助线
you're using Windows or Linux you can
您正在使用Windows或Linux，可以
get your ruler by pressing Ctrl r or if
通过按Ctrl r或如果
you're using Mac you could press command
您正在使用Mac，您可以按下命令
R and there we have the ruler on the
在那里我们把尺子放在
screen
筛网
so with the ruler enabled I'm going to
所以启用尺子后，我将
bring my cursor to the top edge of the
将我的光标移到
ruler and click and drag down to create
标尺并单击并向下拖动可创建
a guide like that
像那样的导游
and now I'm going to change the angle of
现在我要改变角度
this guide by hovering my cursor over
本指南通过将我的光标悬停在
until it highlights red and then double
直到它高亮显示红色，然后加倍
clicking it and then we'll get this menu
点击它，我们就会看到这个菜单
here where we can change the angle if
在这里我们可以更改角度，如果
you see right here we have angle and
你看，就在这里，我们有角度
this the angle is set to zero so I'm
这个角度被设置为零，所以我
going to change this to my measurement
我要把这个换成我的尺寸
which is 36.95 and I will press ok
电话号码是36.95，我会按OK
and now I can take this guide and I can
现在我可以带着这个向导，我可以
place it up against the edge of the
把它放在边上
design there and now I can make a
在那里设计，现在我可以做一个
duplicate of this guide I can double
这本指南的副本我可以翻倍
click it again and I can go to duplicate
再次单击它，我就可以转到复制
and I can take this duplicate copy and I
我可以拿到这份复制品，然后我
can place this on the bottom Edge right
我可以把这个放在右下角
here
这里
let me just move in a little closer here
让我搬到离这里近一点的地方
and make sure that that is a little more
并确保这是更多的一点
accurate
准确
okay that's better
好的，这样好多了。
now you may be wondering if we have to
现在你可能在想我们是不是必须
create more guides for this side
为这一侧创建更多辅助线
normally we would but with this design
通常我们会这样做，但有了这个设计
this design is symmetrical so we won't
这个设计是对称的，所以我们不会
have to do that we can just create the
必须这样做，我们只需创建
left hand side and then make a duplicate
在左手边，然后复制
copy and mirror it over here to the
复制并将其镜像到这里
right hand side so we're good with these
右手边，所以我们很擅长这些
guides as it is let's trace the rest of
原封不动的向导，让我们来追踪其余的
this logo I'm going to grab my bezier
这个标志我要去拿我的贝塞尔
pen by pressing B on the keyboard and I
通过按键盘上的B键和I键来输入
want to make sure I have the proper
想确保我有合适的
setting enabled
已启用设置
and I'm going to start the line halfway
我要把这条线开到一半
through the design right here first let
通过这里的设计，首先让我们
me turn on snapping so I can snap to the
我打开捕捉，这样我就可以捕捉到
guide
指南
I'm going to snap right there
我要在这里抓紧时间
and then hold Ctrl and bring the line
然后按住Ctrl键并将线条
straight up to the other guide and click
直接转到其他指南，然后单击
again
再来一次
and then I'm going to bring this line
然后我要把这条线
all the way out here I want this to I
一路走来，我想让这一切成为我
want this to really stick out far
想要这个真的很突出吗？
because we're going to trim off the
因为我们要修剪掉
edges I'm going to bring this out here
我要把这个带到这里来
and then I'll snap to this line again
然后我会再次按下这条线
and then I'll come back to the starting
然后我会回到起点
point over here like that
像这样指着这里
and now we've completed the shape
现在我们已经完成了形状
so now let's complete the rest of the
现在让我们来完成剩下的
design I'm going to turn off snapping
设计我要关闭捕捉
let me fill in this shape here I'm going
让我填一下这个形状，我要走了
to give this a color I'm going to remove
为了给它配上一种我要去掉的颜色
The Stroke by holding shift and clicking
按住Shift键并单击的笔划
this red X down here and I'll bring down
这个红色的X在这里，我会把它拿下来
the opacity of this as well so I can see
这也是不透明的，所以我可以看到
what's going on beneath it
它下面发生了什么？
and now I'm going to create another
现在我要创造另一个
shape for this leg of the logo right
徽标右腿的形状
here I'm going to come over here to my
在这里，我要走到我的
rectangle tool and I'm going to click
矩形工具，然后我将单击
and drag to create a rectangle that goes
并拖动以创建一个矩形，该矩形
over the top like that I want this to
像这样过了头，我希望这件事
stick out as well and then I'm going to
我也会脱颖而出然后我会
zoom in on this let me make this a
放大这个，让我把它变成一个
different color so I could differentiate
不同的颜色，这样我就能区分
it
它
and I'm going to grab my select tool and
我要拿起我的选择工具
I'm going to come down here and zoom in
我要下来把它放大
a lot just so I can make sure that I get
很多，这样我就能确保我得到
an accurate placement on the edge of the
一个准确的放置在
logo there and I did that for the bottom
徽标在那里，我为底部做了这个
Edge I'll come over here and do this for
边缘我会到这里来做这件事
the right Edge as well
右翼也是如此
I'm going to change this width right
我要把这个宽度改对了
here
这里
and then I'll do the same over here for
然后我会在这里做同样的事情
the left Edge I'm going to make sure
左边缘我要确保
everything is accurate or as close as it
每件事都是准确的或尽可能接近的
can be sometimes it's a little different
有时会有一点不同
a little difficult when you have
当你遇到困难的时候
pixelation
像素化
and now I'm going to trim off these
现在我要把这些都剪掉
unwanted edges there's various ways that
不想要的边缘有各种各样的方法
we can do this but for this particular
如果不是因为这个特殊情况，我们可以这么做。
logo I'm just going to select both of
我要同时选择两个徽标
these objects and go to path and select
这些对象，然后转到路径并选择
fracture
骨折
and now I can take this object and get
现在我可以拿着这个物体
rid of it and then I can take this
扔掉它，然后我就可以拿着这个了
object right here and get rid of that as
对象在这里，并将其作为
well and now we can turn off the
好了，现在我们可以关闭
visibility of the guides because they're
导游的可见性，因为它们是
just getting in the way now by pressing
现在只是通过按下来挡路
the vertical Bar Key so I'm going to
垂直条形键，所以我要
hold shift and press the vertical Bar
按住Shift键并按竖线
Key to turn off the visibility and now
关闭可见性和现在的键
let's round these edges
让我们绕过这些边
so let me zoom in on this if you notice
如果你注意到的话让我来放大这个
now we have three different shapes that
现在我们有三种不同的形状
make up the left hand side of that logo
组成那个徽标的左手边
so let me zoom in over here let me go to
所以让我放大这里，让我转到
my edit pads my nodes tool
我的编辑板我的节点工具
and I'm going to enable the corners life
我要让角落里的人
path effect and we're going to get these
路径效应，我们将得到这些
round knots here and I'm going to take
在这里打个圆结，我要把
this round knot and I'm going to click
这个圆结，我要点击
and drag this down until this corner
然后把这个往下拖到这个角落
matches the Contour of the logo there
与那里的徽标轮廓相匹配
just like that and that looks pretty
就像那样，看起来很漂亮
good so I'll finalize that by going to
很好，那么我将通过以下方式完成
path and selecting object to path and
路径并选择要进行路径的对象，然后
then I'll come down here and do the same
然后我会来这里做同样的事情
thing I'm going to click on this object
我要点击这个物体
and I'm going to enable the live path
我将启用活动路径
effect again the corners life path
再次影响角落的生活道路
effect and then I'll take this knot and
效果，然后我要这个结，然后
then I will bring this down until this
那我就把这个拿下来，直到这个
matches the Contour of this left hand
与这只左手的轮廓匹配
side right there
就在那边
and then I'll finalize that by going to
然后，我将通过以下方式最终确定
path object to path and now we can zoom
路径对象到路径，现在我们可以缩放
out and at this point the left hand side
在这一点上，左手边
of the design is finished we now just
的设计已经完成了，我们现在只是
have to duplicate it and mirror it to
必须复制它并将其镜像到
the other side so let me grab my
另一边，所以让我拿起我的
selection tool let me take this take all
选择工具让我把这一切都拿走
of these objects and move them over here
并把它们移到这里来
let me bring the opacity of them all the
让我把他们所有人的不透明
way up
一路走高
and then I'll bring the opacity of the
然后我会带来不透明的
original logo all the way up as well
原来的徽标也一直向上
because we're going to color this in in
因为我们要给这件事上色
a minute
一分钟
and I'll move this over as a matter of
我会把这件事作为一个问题
fact so I don't run out of canvas space
事实，所以我不会用完画布空间
and now I'm going to duplicate this I'm
现在我要复制这个，我是
going to right click it and go to
右键单击它，然后转到
duplicate
复本
I'm going to bring this over here I want
我要把这个拿过来，我想
to flip this horizontally with this
要用这个水平翻转这个
button right here or you can just press
按钮就在这里，或者你可以直接按
the letter H on the keyboard
键盘上的字母H
and I'm going to enable snapping again
我将再次启用快照
and I'm just going to snap these two
我要拍下这两张照片
together
在一起
and now I want to unify these two pieces
现在我想把这两件事统一起来
together because this is actually one
因为这实际上是一个
piece as you can see in here so I'm
就像你在这里看到的那样，所以我
going to select this object hold shift
要选择此对象，请按住Shift
select this object and go to path
选择此对象并转到路径
Union
友联市
and now all we have to do is Select each
现在我们要做的就是选择每一个
object and grab our dropper tool and
对象并抓起我们的滴管工具
change its color so I'm going to select
更改它的颜色，这样我将选择
I'm going to start with this object
我将从这个对象开始
right here I'm going to grab the dropper
就在这里，我要拿起滴管
tool which is located over here or I'm
工具放在这里，否则我就
just going to use a keyboard shortcut
只需使用键盘快捷键
which is the letter d and then I will
哪个是字母d，然后我会
just sample that area right there to
只需对那里的区域进行采样即可
make that the same color and then I'll
把它做成同样的颜色，然后我就
go back to my select tool by pressing
通过按返回到我的选择工具
the letter s select this object and then
字母S选择该对象，然后
back to the dropper by pressing the
通过按下键返回到滴管
letter d and I'll do the same thing I'll
字母d和我会做同样的事情
just toggle back and forth between those
只需在这些之间来回切换
two tools and fill in the rest of my
两个工具，然后填上我的其余部分
colors like this
像这样的颜色
and just like that we have created a
就像这样，我们创建了一个
vector copy of the Gmail logo so that's
Gmail徽标的矢量副本，因此
just one example of when the measurement
这只是一个例子，当测量
tool can come in handy in inkscape
Inkscape中的工具可以派上用场
if you found this lesson useful then
如果你觉得这一课很有用，那么
consider checking out my inkscape master
考虑一下我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos where I go over all of the tools
我浏览了所有工具的视频
and features in inkscape and I explain
和Inkscape中的功能，我解释
what they are and demonstrate how they
它们是什么并演示它们如何
work kind of like how I did in this
就像我在这件事上做的那样
video we even have a private Community
视频我们甚至有一个私人社区
where you can ask questions and get help
在这里您可以提出问题并获得帮助
from me anytime you want and best of all
随时从我这里收到，最好的是
there's no monthly membership fees you
没有每月会员费
just pay 17 one time and you're in for
只需一次支付17美元，您就能获得
Life I'll have some information about
生活我会有一些信息
that down below if you want to check
如果你想检查的话，请在下面
that out as always thanks for watching
一如既往地感谢收看
oh
哦